pdfbooksworld.com 2017-06-24

# PDFBooksWorld Privacy Policy

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

We recognize the importance of protecting your privacy and our policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site. This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.

 **Membership Registration**

Contents and eBooks in this website may not be suitable for all readers. Only readers above 13 years of age can use our website through membership registration. PDFBooksWorld reserves the right to deny or deactivate memberships anytime now or in future without assigning any reasons.

 **Download Limitations For Free Members (2 Books Per Day)**

Excessive download of books are not allowed for free members and if we notice, such user's IP will be blocked permanently from accessing our site.  **  
**

 **Inactive Accounts**

Accounts without any activity for more than 30 days will be automatically removed by our system.  **  
**

 **Usage of PDF files**

PDF files download from our site is for personal reading only.  Members are not allowed to transfer or store them in any form other than their personal computers or eReaders. **  
**

**Sharing and Selling Information**  

We do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a member (such as email addresses or Name) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested.

 **Children Under 13**  
Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that children (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. We are in compliance with the requirements of [COPPA](http://www.coppa.org/) (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act): we do not collect personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are aged above 13 years.

 **Cookies**

This website uses so called cookies to enhance your user-experience. As you visit and browse our Web site, the site uses cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our clients. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to us in your cookies.

 **Advertisement Serving**

This website may display advertisements from third party ad networks. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website.

The [DoubleClick cookie](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/answer.py?answer=2839090) is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to this website's users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Users also can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

 **Policy Modifications**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

This document was last updated on February 22, 2014
